quiettimediary.com 2012-09-20

# Privacy Policy - Word of Life Fellowship

Date of Last Revision: February 23, 2011

**What information do we collect?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or register for an event or camp or apply at the Bible Institute. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To personalize your experience - (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)

To improve our website - (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)

To improve customer service - (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)

To process transactions - Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

To send periodic emails - The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

To manage and administer the Bible Institute Enrollment Process - All information is used to determine enrollment process and acceptance. Information will be used to help determine financial need, scholarships, and grants. At no time will the information be used other than the sole purpose of the Bible Institute Enrollment Process.

**How do we protect your information?**   
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

We may contact your payment source issuer, law enforcement, or impacted third parties (including other users) and share details of any payments you are associated with if we believe doing so may prevent financial loss or a violation of law.

**Do we use cookies?**   
We do use cookies when you visit our website. This allows us to recognize your computer the next time you visit us. Most Internet browsers are set to accept these cookies automatically.

The type of information we collect as a result of a cookie is specific to your computer and may include the Internet Protocol (IP) address, the date and time you access our website and what parts of the website are visited. We do not however store any sort of user identifiable information. We collect the foregoing information to monitor the usage and usefulness of our website, for statistical purposes. You may set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie or to refuse receiving it. Be aware that in such event you may limit some of the features of our website that are available to you.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**   
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**   
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**   
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act); we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**   
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Your Consent**   
By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.wol.org/content/privacy "WOL Privacy Statement").

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**   
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**   
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Word of Life Fellowship, Inc.  
P.O. Box 600  
Schroon Lake, NY 12870  
U.S.A.  
info@wol.org  
518.494.6000
